<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BeTrack</string>
    <string name="splash_loading">Loading...</string>

    <!-- start activity_start_study -->
    <string name="disclaimer_error">You need to agree to go on with the study</string>

    <!-- Disclaimer to accept to participate the study -->
    <string name="disclaimer_title">Participant Consent Form</string>
    <string name="disclaimer">
        Principal Investigator: Dr. Frances Chen, UBC Department of Psychology (Tel: 604-822-2549)
        Co-Investigator: Dr. Christine Anderl, UBC Department of Psychology (Tel: 778-919-9819)
        1. Introduction: In this study we are interested in whether online social behaviour varies across the natural female menstrual cycle. This consent form describes what will happen to you during the study; it will also describe any possible benefits, risks, and discomforts. Before making a decision whether to participate or not, please read the following information carefully.
        2. What is the purpose of the study?: The purpose of this study is to examine whether online social behaviour varies across the menstrual cycle.
        3. What procedures does the study involve?: In this study you will be invited to the Social Health Lab for an initial 30-minute lab session where you will be introduced to the study by a research assistant, asked to complete some questionnaires, and install and set up a research application on your smartphone with the help of the research assistant.
        You will then be asked to fill in a daily 1-minute questionnaire asking about the activities you engaged in that day directly on your smartphone for 35 days. Throughout these 35 days, the application will also record information about your phone usage such as how long and how often you use your phone in general and how long and how often you use several specific social applications (Tinder, WhatsApp, Facebook, Facebook Messenger, SnapChat, and Instagram); no content-related information about what you do when using these applications will be recorded.
        Finally, you will be invited back to the Social Health Lab so that the research assistant can explain the study to you and answer any questions that you might have.
        4. Your participation is voluntary: Your participation is entirely voluntary; it is up to you to decide whether or not to take part in this study. If you wish to participate, you will be asked to install and set up the application. If you do decide to take part in this study, you are free to withdraw at any time and without giving any reasons for your decision. If you do not wish to participate, you do not have to provide any reason for your decision not to participate.
        5.  What are the possible risks or discomforts?: We do not foresee any risks in participating in this study. Still, please be reminded that you may choose not to answer any questions that you do not wish to answer, and that you are free to withdraw at any time. (If any issues do arise as a result of your participation, please contact Dr. Chen. Her telephone number is listed above.)
        6.  What are the benefits of participating in this study?: As a result of participating in this research, you will be given the opportunity to learn more about your individual smartphone use. More specifically, upon completion of the study, we will provide you with individual feedback on how much time you spend per day using your smartphone in general and the dating and communication apps listed above.
        7. Will I receive any tangible rewards for participating in this study?: Through UBC’s Human Subjects Pool, you will receive 2 HSP credits for your participation in this study.
        8.  Your responses will be kept strictly confidential: All of the information you provide will be kept strictly confidential. All electronic study data will be encrypted before being sent from your smartphone to a password-protected server and then stored on encrypted and password-protected computers and/or locked laboratory facilities in the Department of Psychology at the University of British Columbia. Access to all data collected during the study will be restricted to Dr. Chen and her research team. All data (both online and paper formats) will be kept for at least five years and destroyed when it is no longer needed. In line with current best practices in psychological research, electronic data will be preserved for future use in open science initiatives. Open science initiatives allow for researchers from different universities to share their data upon completion of studies, in an effort to stimulate further use and exploration of existing data sets. Data is uploaded to an online form in the form of a computer software file (e.g., SPSS), and these files are stripped of any information that could identify you (e.g., names) to ensure confidentiality and anonymity.
        9.  Who do I contact if I have questions about the study?: If you have any concerns or complaints about your rights as a research participant and/or your experiences while participating in this study, contact the Research Participant Complaint Line in the UBC Office of Research Ethics at 604-822-8598 or if long distance e-mail RSIL@ors.ubc.ca or call toll free 1-877-822-8598. If you have general questions about the study, you can call Dr. Frances Chen, the principal investigator of this study. Dr. Frances Chen may be reached at 604-822-2549.
        10. Subject consent to participate: I have read and understood the consent form. I have had the time and opportunity to ask questions and have had satisfactory responses to my questions. I understand that my participation in this study is voluntary and that I am completely free to refuse to participate or to withdraw from this study at any time. To withdraw from this study during the data collection phase, it will be sufficient for me to uninstall the app; if I do so, my data will be deleted by the researchers prior to any analysis. If I choose to withdraw from the study at a later time (i.e., after data collection has been completed), I can ask Dr. Chen, the principal investigator of this study (604-822-2549), to delete my data; for my data to be identified and deleted, I will need to indicate my personal study ID (a unique, random number that only I know and that I can find in the settings menu of the app). I freely consent to participate in this study. By installing and setting up the application on my personal smartphone, I am indicating that I agree to participate in the study.
        By installing and setting up the application on your personal smartphone, you are consenting to participate in this research.
    </string>
    <string name="disclaimer_agree">I agree to participate in this research.</string>

    <!-- Study informations -->
    <string name="study_title">Phone Use Study</string>
    <string name="study_description">Utque aegrum corpus quassari etiam levibus solet offensis, ita animus eius angustus et tener, quicquid increpuisset, ad salutis suae dispendium existimans factum aut cogitatum, insontium caedibus fecit victoriam luctuosam.
        Pandente itaque viam fatorum sorte tristissima, qua praestitutum erat eum vita et imperio spoliari, itineribus interiectis permutatione iumentorum emensis venit Petobionem oppidum Noricorum, ubi reseratae sunt insidiarum latebrae omnes, et Barbatio repente apparuit comes, qui sub eo domesticis praefuit, cum Apodemio agente in rebus milites ducens, quos beneficiis suis oppigneratos elegerat imperator certus nec praemiis nec miseratione ulla posse deflecti.
        Rogatus ad ultimum admissusque in consistorium ambage nulla praegressa inconsiderate et leviter proficiscere inquit ut praeceptum est, Caesar sciens quod si cessaveris, et tuas et palatii tui auferri iubebo prope diem annonas. hocque solo contumaciter dicto subiratus abscessit nec in conspectum eius postea venit saepius arcessitus.
        Quaestione igitur per multiplices dilatata fortunas cum ambigerentur quaedam, non nulla levius actitata constaret, post multorum clades Apollinares ambo pater et filius in exilium acti cum ad locum Crateras nomine pervenissent, villam scilicet suam quae ab Antiochia vicensimo et quarto disiungitur lapide, ut mandatum est, fractis cruribus occiduntur.
        Harum trium sententiarum nulli prorsus assentior. Nec enim illa prima vera est, ut, quem ad modum in se quisque sit, sic in amicum sit animatus. Quam multa enim, quae nostra causa numquam faceremus, facimus causa amicorum! precari ab indigno, supplicare, tum acerbius in aliquem invehi insectarique vehementius, quae in nostris rebus non satis honeste, in amicorum fiunt honestissime; multaeque res sunt in quibus de suis commodis viri boni multa detrahunt detrahique patiuntur, ut iis amici potius quam ipsi fruantur.
        Quam ob rem cave Catoni anteponas ne istum quidem ipsum, quem Apollo, ut ais, sapientissimum iudicavit; huius enim facta, illius dicta laudantur. De me autem, ut iam cum utroque vestrum loquar, sic habetote.
        Horum adventum praedocti speculationibus fidis rectores militum tessera data sollemni armatos omnes celeri eduxere procursu et agiliter praeterito Calycadni fluminis ponte, cuius undarum magnitudo murorum adluit turres, in speciem locavere pugnandi. neque tamen exiluit quisquam nec permissus est congredi. formidabatur enim flagrans vesania manus et superior numero et ruitura sine respectu salutis in ferrum.
        Huic Arabia est conserta, ex alio latere Nabataeis contigua; opima varietate conmerciorum castrisque oppleta validis et castellis, quae ad repellendos gentium vicinarum excursus sollicitudo pervigil veterum per oportunos saltus erexit et cautos. haec quoque civitates habet inter oppida quaedam ingentes Bostram et Gerasam atque Philadelphiam murorum firmitate cautissimas. hanc provinciae inposito nomine rectoreque adtributo obtemperare legibus nostris Traianus conpulit imperator incolarum tumore saepe contunso cum glorioso marte Mediam urgeret et Parthos.
        Haec et huius modi quaedam innumerabilia ultrix facinorum impiorum bonorumque praemiatrix aliquotiens operatur Adrastia atque utinam semper quam vocabulo duplici etiam Nemesim appellamus: ius quoddam sublime numinis efficacis, humanarum mentium opinione lunari circulo superpositum, vel ut definiunt alii, substantialis tutela generali potentia partilibus praesidens fatis, quam theologi veteres fingentes Iustitiae filiam ex abdita quadam aeternitate tradunt omnia despectare terrena.
        Ac ne quis a nobis hoc ita dici forte miretur, quod alia quaedam in hoc facultas sit ingeni, neque haec dicendi ratio aut disciplina, ne nos quidem huic uni studio penitus umquam dediti fuimus. Etenim omnes artes, quae ad humanitatem pertinent, habent quoddam commune vinculum, et quasi cognatione quadam inter se continentur.
    </string>
    <string name="study_agree">I agree to participate in this research.</string>

    <!-- reminder study -->
    <string name="study_reminder">REMINDER</string>
    <string name="study_reminder_question">From tomorrow on you will be notified every day to fill in a survey </string>


    <!-- Network error -->
        <string name="network_error_title">Network connection error</string>
        <string name="network_title_in_progress">Network connection</string>
        <string name="network_error_start_text">Please connect your phone to the internet. It is mandatory to have an internet connection to register for a new study</string>
        <string name="network_end_text">Data transfer in progress</string>
        <string name="network_error_end_text">Please connect your phone to the internet. It is mandatory to have an internet connection for the last day of the study</string>
        <string name="network_retry">Retry</string>

        <!-- Network loading -->
        <string name="network_loading">Loading...</string>

    <!-- end activity_start_study -->



    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Study welcome screen -->
    <string name="welcome_title">BeTrack</string>
    <string name="welcome_select">Select which study you want to join:</string>
    <string name="welcome_title_description">Description:</string>
    <string name="welcome_description">Blabblah</string>
    <string name="welcome_start">START</string>
    <string name="welcome_loading">Loading</string>
    <string name="welcome_wait">Please wait...</string>

    <!-- Study main screen -->
    <string name="Betrack_welcome">Thank you for participating and see you again tomorrow!</string>
    <string name="Betrack_info_start">Days remaining:</string>
    <string name="Betrack_start">Thank you for setting up the app! The daily surveys will start tomorrow.</string>
    <string name="Betrack_end">Thank you for your participation in the study. Please contact us at: smartphonestudy@psych.ubc.ca </string>
    <string name="Betrack_battery_manager">You seem to use a battery manager, please whitelist BeTrack or contact the Social Health Lab at: smartphonestudy@psych.ubc.ca </string>
    <string name="Betrack_info_end">Your phone usage:</string>
    <string name="Betrack_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Your personnal ID-->
    <string name="pref_header_your_id">Your personnal ID </string>

    <!-- General settings -->
    <string name="pref_header_general">General</string>
    <string name="pref_key_study_enable"> Betrack.Settings.StudyEnable </string>
    <string name="pref_title_enable_study">Enable study</string>
    <string name="pref_description_enable_study">Allow to be temporarily or permanently out of the study
    </string>
    <string name="pref_consent_title">Consent form link
    </string>
    <string name="pref_consent_description"> https://osf.io/em83w
    </string>
    <string name="pref_contact_title">Lab e-mail address
    </string>
    <string name="pref_contact_description">smartphonestudy@psych.ubc.ca
    </string>

    <!-- Settings for Data & Sync -->
    <string name="pref_header_data_sync">Data &amp; sync</string>
    <string name="pref_key_data_sync_enable_usage_3g"> Betrack.Settings.EnableDataUsage </string>
    <string name="pref_title_enable_usage_3g">Enable usage of 3G/LTE to transfer study data</string>
    <string name="pref_description_enable_usage_3g">Allow to use the 3G/LTE connection to transfer data of the study to our server
    </string>

    <!-- Settings for Notifications -->
    <string name="pref_header_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="pref_key_study_notification"> Betrack.Settings.StudyNotification </string>
    <string name="pref_key_study_notification_time"> Betrack.Settings.StudyNotificationTime </string>
    <string name="pref_title_new_message_notifications">Study notifications</string>
    <string name="pref_notification_time">Time of the notification</string>

    <!-- Credits-->
    <string name="pref_header_credits">Credits </string>
    <string name="pref_header_credits_title1">Thanks to Philipp Jahoda</string>
    <string name="pref_header_credits_text1">for MPChartLib</string>
    <string name="pref_header_credits_title2">Thanks to Mark Murphy</string>
    <string name="pref_header_credits_text2">for location poller</string>
    <string name="pref_header_credits_title3">Thanks to Francesco Cannizzaro</string>
    <string name="pref_header_credits_text3">for material stepper form</string>
    <string name="pref_header_credits_title4">Thanks to http://www.flaticon.com/</string>
    <string name="pref_header_credits_text4">for their awesome sets of icons</string>

    <!-- Informations about the study-->
    <string name="pref_header_info">Informations about the study </string>

    <!-- set up Betrack -->
    <string name="Betrack_setup_title">Set up your BeTrack application</string>
    <string name="Betrack_setup_text">Almost there. To be a part of the study we need specific permission on your phone please follow the steps below. Moreover if you use a battery manager please make sure that we are white listed</string>

    <!-- UsageStat enable -->
    <string name="UsageStat_enable_title">Enable Usage Stat</string>
    <string name="UsageStat_enable_text">When you will click on the OK button of that window, the setting menu of your phone will be open. In that menu please allow BeTrack to access the statistics of your phone. When you are done get back to BeTrack and you\'ll be able to start the study.</string>
    <string name="UsageStat_ok">USAGE STAT</string>


    <!-- notification -->
    <string name="notification_title">BeTrack</string>
    <string name="notification_desc">Please fill in our little daily survey</string>
    <string name="notification_running">Betrack is running</string>

    <!-- Huawei protected app -->
    <string name="huawei_title">Huawei Protected Apps</string>
    <string name="huawei_desc">requires to be enabled in Protected Apps to function properly.</string>
    <string name="huawei_positive_button">PROTECTED APPS</string>
    <string name="huawei_check">Do not show again</string>

    <!-- GPS Enable -->
    <string name="gps_enable_title">GPS Enable</string>
    <string name="gps_enable_desc">We need to have to your positioning information to function properly</string>
    <string name="gps_enable_positive_button">ENABLE THE GPS</string>

    <!-- Battery white list Enable -->
    <string name="battery_enable_title">Battery Optimizations</string>
    <string name="battery_enable_desc">We need to have to be whitelisted to be able to be exempt from battery optimization</string>
    <string name="battery_enable_positive_button">Whitelist betrack</string>

    <!-- Surveys -->
    <string name="question_error">You need to answer that question</string>
    <string name="survey_age">\u0020years old</string>
    <string name="survey_days">\u0020days</string>
    <string name="survey_hours">\u0020hour(s)</string>
    <string name="survey_minutes">\u0020minute(s)</string>
    <string name="survey_days_left">days left</string>
    <string name="survey_day_left">day left</string>

    <!-- Start survey -->

    <!-- Screen 1 -->
    <string name="title_ss_screen1">Age</string>
    <string name="question_ss_screen1">How old are you?</string>

    <!-- Screen 2 -->
    <string name="title_ss_screen2">Ethnicity</string>
    <string name="question_ss_screen2">What is your ethnicity/ethnic background?</string>
    <string name="option1_ss_screen2">Caucasian</string>
    <string name="option2_ss_screen2">Hispanic/Latino</string>
    <string name="option3_ss_screen2">African</string>
    <string name="option4_ss_screen2">East Asian (e.g., Chinese, Japanese, or Korean)</string>
    <string name="option5_ss_screen2">Southeast Asian (e.g., Vietnamese, Filipino)</string>
    <string name="option6_ss_screen2">South Asian (e.g., Indian)</string>
    <string name="option7_ss_screen2">Middle Eastern (e.g, Persian)</string>
    <string name="option8_ss_screen2">Aboriginal</string>
    <string name="option9_ss_screen2">Other</string>

    <!-- Screen 3 -->
    <string name="title_ss_screen3">Ethnicity</string>
    <string name="question_ss_screen3">Please specify your ethnicity:</string>

    <!-- Screen 4 -->
    <string name="title_ss_screen4">Student</string>
    <string name="question_ss_screen4">Are you classified as an international student by our university?</string>

    <!-- Screen 5 -->
    <string name="title_ss_screen5">English Level</string>
    <string name="question_ss_screen5">Are you a native speaker of English?</string>

    <!-- Screen 6 -->
    <string name="title_ss_screen6">English Level</string>
    <string name="question_ss_screen6">How long have you been speaking English (in years)?</string>

    <!-- Screen 7 -->
    <string name="title_ss_screen7">English Level</string>
    <string name="question_ss_screen7">Do you consider yourself fluent in English?</string>

    <!-- Screen 8 -->
    <string name="title_ss_screen8">English Level</string>
    <string name="question_ss_screen8">If English is not your first language, what test did you take to satisfy the UBC English Language Admission Requirement?</string>
    <string name="option1_ss_screen8">TOEFL</string>
    <string name="option2_ss_screen8">IELTS</string>
    <string name="option3_ss_screen8">other</string>

    <!-- Screen 9 -->
    <string name="title_ss_screen9">English Level</string>
    <string name="question_ss_screen9">Please specify the English test you took:</string>

    <!-- Screen 10 -->
    <string name="title_ss_screen10">English Level</string>
    <string name="question_ss_screen10">Please report your score:</string>

    <!-- Screen 11 -->
    <string name="title_ss_screen11">University</string>
    <string name="question_ss_screen11">What year are you in university?</string>
    <string name="option1_ss_screen11">I am a first year student at UBC</string>
    <string name="option2_ss_screen11">I am a second year student at UBC</string>
    <string name="option3_ss_screen11">I am a third year student at UBC</string>
    <string name="option4_ss_screen11">I am a fourth year student at UBC</string>
    <string name="option5_ss_screen11">Other</string>

    <!-- Screen 12 -->
    <string name="title_ss_screen12">University</string>
    <string name="question_ss_screen12">Did you transfer to UBC from another post-secondary institution?</string>

    <!-- Screen 13 -->
    <string name="title_ss_screen13">University</string>
    <string name="question_ss_screen13">Please specify?</string>

    <!-- Screen 14 -->
    <string name="title_ss_screen14">Relationship</string>
    <string name="question_ss_screen14">Are you currently in a romantic/sexual relationship?</string>
    <string name="option1_ss_screen14">Yes, I am in an exclusive romantic/sexual relationship</string>
    <string name="option2_ss_screen14">Yes, I am in a non-exclusive romantic/sexual relationship</string>
    <string name="option3_ss_screen14">No</string>

    <!-- Screen 15 -->
    <string name="title_ss_screen15">Contraception</string>
    <string name="question_ss_screen15">Are you currently on any form of hormonal birth control (or do you intend on going on hormonal birth control within the next six weeks)?</string>

    <!-- Screen 16 -->
    <string name="title_ss_screen16">Maternity</string>
    <string name="question_ss_screen16">Are you currently pregnant or breastfeeding?</string>

    <!-- Screen 17 -->
    <string name="title_ss_screen17">Period</string>
    <string name="question_ss_screen17">How long does your menstrual cycle (i.e., the number of days between the first day of your period until the last day before the onset of your next period) last on average?</string>

    <!-- Screen 18 -->
    <string name="title_ss_screen18">Period</string>
    <string name="question_ss_screen18">How long did your last menstrual cycle (i.e., the number of days between the first day of your period until the last day before the onset of your next period) last?</string>

    <!-- Screen 19 -->
    <string name="title_ss_screen19">Period</string>
    <string name="question_ss_screen19">When did your current/last period start? Please provide an exact date if possible:</string>

    <!-- Screen 20 -->
    <string name="title_ss_screen20">Period</string>
    <string name="question_ss_screen20">When do you expect your next period to start? Please provide an exact date if possible:</string>

    <!-- Daily survey -->
    <!-- Screen 1 (Period) -->
    <string name="title_sd_screen1">Period</string>
    <string name="question_sd_screen1">Are you on your period today?</string>

    <!-- Screen 2 (Clothes) -->
    <string name="title_sd_screen2">Clothes</string>
    <string name="question_sd_screen2">Which are the dominant colors of the shirt/ dress you are wearing (max. 3)?</string>

    <!-- Screen 3 (ACTIVITIES) -->
    <string name="title_sd_screen3">Activities (1/2)</string>
    <string name="question_sd_screen3">Which of the following activities did you engage in yesterday?</string>
    <string name="answer1_sd_screen3">working</string>
    <string name="answer2_sd_screen3">studying</string>
    <string name="answer3_sd_screen3">reading</string>
    <string name="answer4_sd_screen3">watching tv</string>
    <string name="answer5_sd_screen3">sports</string>
    <string name="answer6_sd_screen3">shopping</string>

    <!-- Screen 4 (ACTIVITIES 2/2) -->
    <string name="title_sd_screen4">Activities (2/2)</string>
    <string name="question_sd_screen4">Which of the following activities did you engage in yesterday?</string>
    <string name="answer1_sd_screen4">meeting friends</string>
    <string name="answer2_sd_screen4">having drinks</string>
    <string name="answer3_sd_screen4">clubbing</string>
    <string name="answer4_sd_screen4">dating</string>
    <string name="answer5_sd_screen4">sex</string>
    <string name="answer6_sd_screen4">kissing</string>

    <!-- Screen 5 (Mood) -->
    <string name="title_sd_screen5">Mood</string>
    <string name="question_sd_screen5">How are you feeling right now?</string>
    <string name="answer1_sd_screen5">Good</string>
    <string name="answer2_sd_screen5">Relaxed</string>
    <string name="answer3_sd_screen5">Active</string>

    <!-- End survey -->
    <!-- Screen 1 -->
    <string name="title_se_screen1">Relationship</string>
    <string name="question_se_screen1">Has your relationship status changed throughout the study?</string>
    <string name="option1_se_screen1">Yes, I am now in an exclusive romantic/sexual relationship</string>
    <string name="option2_se_screen1">Yes, I am now in a non-exclusive romantic/sexual relationship</string>
    <string name="option3_se_screen1">Yes, I am no longer in a romantic/sexual relationship</string>
    <string name="option4_se_screen1">No</string>

    <!-- Screen 2 -->
    <string name="title_se_screen2">Contraception</string>
    <string name="question_se_screen2">Have you started being on any form of hormonal birth control throughout the study?</string>

    <!-- Screen 3 -->
    <string name="title_se_screen3">Tinder</string>
    <string name="question_se_screen3">How often do you think you used Tinder throughout the study?</string>
    <string name="option1_se_screen3">Every day</string>
    <string name="option2_se_screen3">Several days a week</string>
    <string name="option3_se_screen3">At least once a week</string>
    <string name="option4_se_screen3">Less than once a week</string>
    <string name="option5_se_screen3">Not at all</string>

    <!-- Screen 4 -->
    <string name="title_se_screen4">Phone Usage</string>
    <string name="question_se_screen4">On average, how many hours/minutes per day do you think you spent using your phone in general throughout the study?</string>

    <!-- Screen 5 -->
    <string name="title_se_screen5">Study</string>
    <string name="question_se_screen5">How interesting and engaging was it for you to participate in this study?</string>
    <string name="option1_se_screen5">not at all</string>
    <string name="option2_se_screen5">extremely</string>

    <!-- Screen 6 -->
    <string name="title_se_screen6">Study</string>
    <string name="question_se_screen6">How much did the daily survey interfere with your activities at the time of the alarm?</string>
    <string name="option1_se_screen6">not at all</string>
    <string name="option2_se_screen6">extremely</string>

    <!-- Screen 7 -->
    <string name="title_se_screen7">Study</string>
    <string name="question_se_screen7">Would you have minded if the study period had been longer than 35 days (e.g., two full months)?</string>
    <string name="option1_se_screen7">not at all</string>
    <string name="option2_se_screen7">very much so</string>

    <!-- Screen 8 -->
    <string name="title_se_screen8">Research App</string>
    <string name="question_se_screen8">How easy/difficult was it for you to use the research app?</string>
    <string name="option1_se_screen8">very easy</string>
    <string name="option2_se_screen8">very difficult</string>

    <!-- Screen 9 -->
    <string name="title_se_screen9">Research App</string>
    <string name="question_se_screen9">Is there anything in particular you would change about the research app?</string>

</resources>
